linkeyproject.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy - linkeyproject.com

Privacy Policy

Last modified May 1, 2013

Aztec media inc. ("Linkey Project") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about Linkey Project's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Linkey Project receives, collects and uses information in connection with its website located at www.linkeyproject.com ("Site").

Collection and Use of Information

Information You Provide:

You can use the Site and access software without providing any Personal Information (defined below). However, in connection with other activities through the Site, you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information, which may include your name, email address, age, gender, address, telephone number(s), areas of interest, login name, login password and other self-identifying information (all "Personal Information"). It is entirely optional for you to engage in these activities. Linkey Project collects this Personal Information primarily for the following purposes: (i) to maintain a record of registered users; (ii) to manage the login process and maintain users' personal preferences; (iii) to email registered users with news and updates; and (iv) to email promotional offers. In addition, Linkey Project may also collect information about you in surveys or for sweepstakes and contests on the Site and information about the searches you perform, promotional offers you choose and the pages you visit on the Site. If you no longer wish to receive communication from Linkey Project, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in any of those communications or update your account setting information (see section below on Change or Removal of Information).

Information We Automatically Collect:

Linkey Project does not automatically collect any Personal Information on or through the Site, except as provided by you in connection with the registration process described above. When you use the Site, Linkey Project may also automatically collect certain information about your computer to facilitate, evaluate and verify your use of the Site. For example, Linkey Project may use "cookies," "web beacons" and similar devices to track your activities on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. A web-beacon is a small transparent gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at Linkey Project's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. Linkey Project's use of cookies or similar devices is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

Linkey Project may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Linkey Project collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Linkey Project will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with the aggregate data of its users.

Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Linkey Project does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Linkey Project may disclose your Personal Information if Linkey Project believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Linkey Project; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Linkey Project (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Linkey Project services or members of the public. Linkey Project may share aggregated non-personally identifiable demographic information about users with third party advertising and content companies. This information does not identify individual users and Linkey Project does not link aggregate user data with Personal Information.

Linkey Project may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help it provide, analyze and improve the Site and service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, information processing and improvement of the Site's features and services. These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on behalf of Linkey Project and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.

Third party advertisers and websites

Linkey Project does not actively share Personal Information with third party advertisers for their direct marketing purposes unless you give Linkey Project your consent. Advertisers, however, may obtain public information about you from your user profile and other public sources. Remember, third parties will have access to your Personal Information if you provide it to them. For example, if you want to buy offers, goods or services from through third party advertisers on the Site, the transaction may be facilitated on the third party's website. You will then have to provide the third party with the information required (such as for example name, shipping address, credit card info etc), which will them be subject to their specific privacy policies. If you access another website or promotion and/or service through a website operated by any entity other than Linkey Project, that site is referred to as a "Third Party Site". Unless Linkey Project clearly indicates otherwise at the time of collection, Linkey Project does not share Personal Information with Third Party Sites. Please be aware however that these Third Party Sites may collect information about you. Please see the Third Party Site's privacy policy to better understand what information is collected, how it is used and shared, and your choices regarding control. Linkey Project has no control over these linked Third Party Sites, each of which has a separate privacy and data collection practice, independent of this Privacy Policy. Linkey Project does not monitor, control, or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any Third Party Site. As such, Linkey Project is not responsible for, or have control over, the content or the privacy policies of these Third Party Sites. You must read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit when linking from the Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Linkey Project.

Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). The Site is intended solely for users who are of adult age in their jurisdiction, and any registration by, use of, or access to the Site or services by anyone under the age of majority is unauthorized, unlicensed, and in violation of this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you represent and warrant you are of adult age in your jurisdiction and that you agree to abide by all of the terms and conditions herein. Linkey Project may terminate your account, project, and any content or information that you have posted on the Site and/or prohibit you from using or accessing the Site for any reason, at any time in its sole discretion, with or without notice, including without limitation if Linkey Project believes that you have misrepresented your age. Linkey Project never knowingly collects or maintains information at or on our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of the Site is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13.

Security

Linkey Project takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Linkey Project cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Linkey Project has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

If you contact Linkey Project by e-mail or a "contact us" or similar feature on the Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.

In the unlikely event that Linkey Project believes that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, Linkey Project may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, Linkey Project will endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent Linkey Project has your e-mail address, it may notify you by e-mail. **You consent to use of e-mail as a means of such notification.**

If you prefer to use another method to notify you in this situation, please send an e-mail to [info@linkeyproject.com](mailto:info@linkeyproject.com) with the alternative contact information you wish to be used.

With identity theft a continuing problem, it has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals to send e-mail messages to consumers, purporting to represent a legitimate company such as a bank or on-line merchant, requesting that the consumer provide personal, often sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the e-mail address from which the e-mail appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the web site requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity has come to be known as "phishing." If you receive an e-mail or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your password or credit card information) via e-mail or to a web site that does not seem to be affiliated with this Site, or that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information, and report such request to [info@linkeyproject.com](mailto:info@linkeyproject.com).

IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE SITE FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICES, WHICH ARE GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND LINKEY PROJECT' TERMS OF USE, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER. ADDITIONALLY, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO AND PROCESSED IN COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN IN YOUR COUNTRY.

Data Retention

Linkey Project will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that Linkey Project no longer uses your information to provide you services, you may delete your account by notification to[info@linkeyproject.com](mailto:info@linkeyproject.com). Linkey Project may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with its legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, Linkey Project will try to delete your information quickly and upon request. Please note, however, that there may be latency in deleting information from the Linkey Project servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. In addition, Linkey Project will not delete from its servers files that you may have in common with other users.

Business Transitions

In the event that Linkey Project goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. Linkey Project will post a notice on this Site of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information Linkey Project may have prior to such transfer.

Changes to Policy

From time to time, Linkey Project may revise this Policy. Linkey Project will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Linkey Project collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. If Linkey Project makes a change in its data collection policy that would result in a materially more permissive use of your personally identifiable data, Linkey Project will obtain your prior affirmative consent before implementing the change with respect to your data. You should also visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Notice.

Change or Removal of Information

You can review, update, correct, edit or delete your Personal Information at any time by logging in to your account and editing your profile.

When user registers on the Site, the user may have the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from Linkey Project, including offers, updates and newsletters. If a user chooses not to "opt-in", the user will not receive any communication from Linkey Project. If a user's e-mail address changes, a user may correct such information by sending an e-mail to [support@linkeyproject.com](mailto:support@linkeyproject.com) with the request or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. If a user no longer wishes to receive e-mail communication from Linkey Project, a user may opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. In addition, a user can remove their e-mail address at any time by sending an e-mail with the subject line of OPT-OUT to [support@linkeyproject.com](mailto:support@linkeyproject.com)

Contact Information

If you believe Linkey Project is not adhering to this Privacy Policy or you have any questions in connection with this Privacy Policy, please contact Linkey Project at: [privacy@linkeyproject.com](mailto:privacy@linkeyproject.com) or by writing to Aztec media inc., PO Box 51968, Limassol 3509 Cyprus
